Guide to the Oliver F. Atkins photograph collection, 1943-1975
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Prints, 1943-1974; (48 boxes)
  - Subseries 1.1: Subject, 1940s-1974; (15 boxes)
    - Iwo Jima Memorial, November 10, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Javits, Jacob, 1960s (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Jazwinski, Zdzislaw J., August 1953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      Andrews Air Force Base
    - Jazz concert, 1950s (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Johnson, Louie, June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1950s (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Presidential campaign
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Inauguration
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Oval office
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Lyndon B. Johnson with cabinet members and advisors
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Lyndon B. Johnson with Lady Bird Johnson
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., November 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Lyndon B. Johnson ranch
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., circa 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1960s (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Hubert Humphrey; Pope Paul VI
    - Julius and Ethel Rosenberg protest, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Just what the doctor ordered, December 1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Hospital care in New York City
    - Kefauver, Estes, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy, Edward M., 1960s (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Kennedy, Jacqueline, 1950s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1940s (Box 6, Folder 8)
      World War II
    - Kennedy, John F., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Playing football and sailing
    - Kennedy, John F., 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Kennedy family
    - Kennedy, John F., 1953-1961 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1950s-1960s (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Robert F. Kennedy; Ethel Kennedy; John F. Kennedy family
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961-1963, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Official White House portrait and other portraits
    - Kennedy, John F., 1953-1961 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy, John F., December 1959 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Campaigning in Colorado
    - Kennedy, John F., February 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Campaigning in Wisconsin
    - Kennedy, John F., July 1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Democratic Convention in California
    - Kennedy, John F., September 1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Campaigning
    - Kennedy, John F., September 1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Campaigning in California
    - Kennedy, John F., September 1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Campaigning in Michigan
    - Kennedy, John F., September 1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Campaigning in Texas
    - Kennedy, John F., September 1960 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Campaigning in Washington
    - Kennedy, John F., September 1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Television debate with Richard M. Nixon
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Ceremonies and gatherings
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Meetings with staff and international leaders
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Press conferences
    - Kennedy, John F., January 1961 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, John F., January 1961 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      State of the Union
    - Kennedy, John F., November 1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Funeral
    - Kennedy, John F., 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Assassination and related events
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Labor racketeering hearings; John McClellan
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1960s (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1960s (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Robert F. Kennedy family
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Democratic convention in California; Kenneth O'Donnell and Pierre Salinger
    - Kennedy, Robert F., June 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Presidential campaign announcement
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Presidential campaign in California
    - Kennedy, Robert F., June 1968 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Funeral service
    - Khrushchev, Nikita, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Knowland, William, January 1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Mr. and Mrs. Knowland
    - Korea, 1950s (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Syngman Rhee
    - Korea, May-June 1951 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Two terrible nights with the 23rd
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      General file
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      The fighting French
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      Greeks know how to die
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      How well do Negroes fight
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      The worlds worst railroad headache
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Nurses story; original article manuscript; Far East command press releases
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Machine gunners; article manuscript
    - Independence of Korea, circa 1948 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      The flying poison
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      The Chinese telegraph their punch
    - Japan, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Marines
    - Japan, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Hokkaido story
    - Korea, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Kaesong Conference
    - Korean War, April 1951 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Refugees
    - Korean War, March 1951 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Korean War, March 1951 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      The big thaw
    - Korean War cease fire, July 1951 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Korean War, May 1951 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      The pious killer of Korea; United States Air Force
    - Lake Anne Village in Reston, Virginia, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - The lungs won't have to be ravaged, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Coal miners in White Haven, Pennsylvania and Affinity, West Virginia
    - The man who looks like Truman, January 1951 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Actor Irving Fisher in New York City
    - Mansfield, Michael, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - March on Washington, August 28, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Marshall, Thurgood, 1950s (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Martin, William McChesney, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Mayfield, Catfish, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - McCarthy, Eugene, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1950s (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - McCormack, John W., 1960s (Box 11, Folder 17)
      Everett M. Dirksen
    - McNamara, Robert S., April 1966 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Meany, George, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Mini-skirts, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Mock air raid, June 1954 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      Olney, Maryland
    - The money surgeon, May 1953 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Burned and mutilated currency unit of the Currency Redemption Division of the Treasury Department
    - Morse, Wayne, 1960s (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Mr. Hell on wheels, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      Detroit, Michigan; Northern Virginia; Avon Lake, Ohio; Fruehauf trailer company
    - Mr. Singer's money machine, May 1951 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      Sewing machine use in Tokyo, Japan
    - The multimillionaire nobody knows, December 1950 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Mundt, Karl, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Murder by mail, May 1952 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      United States Postal Inspection Service in Washington, D.C.
    - My customers get garden fever every spring, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Rockville, Maryland
    - The mystery of your murder, January 1952 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Woods Hole, Massachusetts
    - National Cathedral, September 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Washington, D.C.; includes contact sheets and negatives
    - Nehru, Jawaharlal, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Nigeria, November 1960 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1950s (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Nixon, Richard M. and family, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Nobody loves Clarence, February 1950 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Harry Truman; Portrait of Clarence Cannon; Washington, D.C.
    - Objects, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - The old school bus goes adventuring, May 1950 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Ozark, Arkansas students travel to New York City, Philadelphia, and Washington, D.C.
    - Operations Research Office, September 1951 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Chevy Chase and Aberdeen, Maryland; Washington, D.C.
    - O'Toole, George, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Outdoor activity, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Pentagon demonstration, September 1967 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Pentagon protest, October 1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Percy, Charles, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Peterson, Peter G., 1970s (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Poor people's campaign in Washington, D.C., June 1968 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Portraits of Congressmen, 1950s-1960s (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Portraits of unidentified woman in Washington, D.C., 1950s-1960s (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Potter, Charles, November 1952 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Powell, Adam Clayton, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rayburn, Samuel T., 1950s (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Republic of the Congo, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Republican National Convention, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Henry C. Lodge
    - Reuther, Walter and George Meany in Washington, D.C., 1960s (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Rhodesia, December 1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Rickover, Hyman G. in Washington, D.C., 1950s (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1950s-1960s (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Rockwell, George Lincoln, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Rockwell, Norman, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1950s (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1940s (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - The Rosenberg case: Judge Kaufman's two terrible years, June 1953 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Rosenberg execution protest in Washington, D.C.
    - Rusk, Dean, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Salinger, Pierre, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - The Senate's private eye, January 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      John I. Williams and Preston C. Williams
    - The Senator loves a fight, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Tom Connally in Washington, D.C.
    - Senegal, November 1960 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - She teaches Washington to put on airs, August 1953 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      Agnes McCall Parker in Washington, D.C.
    - Smartest dog in Maryland, August 1950 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Bird dogs in Annapolis, Maryland
    - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - So he's going to clean up boxing, January 1952 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      Commissioner Bob Christenberry in New York City
    - South Africa, December 1960 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Stalin's American snoops, November 1950 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      Telegraph agents of the USSR in Washington, D.C.
    - Stevenson, Adlai E., 1960s (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Symington, Stuart, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - They just love to wreck things, February 1957 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Aberdeen Proving Grounds in Aberdeen, Maryland
    - They track down outlaw broadcasters, October 1951 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      Washington, D.C.
    - They've got all the answers, August 1950 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      Government Printing Office in Washington, D.C.; Arlington, Virginia
    - Togoland, November 1960 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - The toughest job feeding Ike, November 1952 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Joint Chiefs of Staff in Washington, D.C.
    - Truman, Harry, 1940s-1950s (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Portrait signed by Truman to Ollie Atkins
    - Truman, Harry, 1940s-1950s (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Unkle Sam's hair shirt crime-buster, August 1954 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Army 82nd airborne division ceremonies, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Capitol Building, January 1959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Senate subway construction
    - The unusual riddle of the oyster, September 1951 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Marine biology in Milford, Connecticut
    - U.S.S. Forrestal fire, July 29, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - U.S.S. North Carolina in Wilmington, North Carolina, 1950s (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Vance, Cyrus, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Von Braun, Wernher, 1950s (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Wallace, George, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Warren commission report, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Librarian with full set of volumes
    - Warren, Earl, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Washington, D.C., buildings and monuments, 1950s-1960s (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Washington, D.C., hearings and events, 1950s (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Washington, D.C., people and places, 1960s (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Washington, D.C., scenes, 1950s-1960s (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Washington, D.C., tourist views, 1950s (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Washington's flossiest hotel, July 1949 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Carlton Hotel; John L. Lewis; Washington, D.C.
    - We flew 8 miles up, March 1950 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      United States Air Force at Patuxent Naval Air Station in Maryland
    - We found Lincoln's lost bank account, November 1952 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Roland T. Carr and William A. Heilprin at Riggs National Bank in Washington, D.C.
    - We tried to clean up Washington's dope racket, August 1953 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Thomas A. Walden in Washington, D.C.
    - We're betting our shirt on the atomic submarine, March 1949 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Submarine in Key West, Florida
    - We're licking the terror of the Artic, June 1952 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Cold weather clothing tests in Lawrence, Massachusetts
    - Whalen, Richard J., 1960s (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - What is the CIA up to?, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      Allen Dulles
    - What makes a military police tough, January 1951 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Camp Gordon, Georgia; U.S. Army Military Police School
    - What would you do with triplets?, November 1951 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Dayton, Ohio; Yellow Springs, Ohio
    - What's so bad about a professor's job, January 1950 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Arthur M. Whitehill and family; Chapel Hill, North Carolina
    - White House, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Why has Washington gone crazy?, June 1950 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Joe McCarthy checking a pone for wire tapping
    - Williams, Edward Bennett, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - World's most glamorous trash heap, February 1952 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Yugoslavia, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 1.2: Nixon White House Subject, 1968-1974, (23 boxes)
    This subseries consists of prints from Atkins's work as Chief White House Photographer during the Richard M. Nixon Administration. The images document life in the White House, press conferences, visiting foreign leaders, presidential visits abroad, vacations, and Nixon's final days in office following his resignation. There are also numerous photographs of the Nixon's wife, Pat, and his daughters, Julie and Tricia.
    - African Americans, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Air Force One, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Armed Forces, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Armed Forces, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Arrivals - State, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Astronauts and Space, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Cabinet, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Cabinet, 1969-1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Cabinet, 1969-1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Cabinet, 1969-1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Campaign, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Campaign, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Campaign, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Campaign, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Campaign, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Campaign, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Copy negative
    - Camp David, 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Cartoons, 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Children, 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Children, 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Church Services and Religious Figures, 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Church Services and Religious Figures, 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Church Services and Religious Figures, 1969-1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Addressing, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Congress - Groups, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Congress - Groups, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Congress - Individual, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Congress - Individual, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Congress - Individual, 1969-1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Congress - Individual, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Convention, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Crowds, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Crowds, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Dedications, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Dinner Parties - White House, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Diplomatic, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Diplomatic, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Diplomatic, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Dogs, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Drugs, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - David Eisenhower, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Mamie Eisenhower, John Eisenhower, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Elderly With President, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Entertainers, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Entertainers, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Family Pictures, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Family Pictures, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Family Pictures, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Governors, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Governors, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Flood - Pennsylvania, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Funerals, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Funerals, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Handicapped, 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Heads Of State - Africa, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Head Of State - Australia, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Heads Of State - Arab, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Heads Of State - France, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Heads Of State - Canada, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Heads Of State - Great Britain, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Heads Of State - India, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Heads Of State - Iran, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Heads Of State - Israel, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Heads Of State - Italy, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Heads Of State - Japan, 1969-1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Head Of State - Netherlands and Belgium, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Heads Of State - Pakistan, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Head Of State - Romania, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Head Of State - Scandinavia, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Head Of State - S.E. Asia, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Head Of State - Spain, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Head Of State - South and Central America, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Head Of State - Turkey, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Head Of State - USSR, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Head Of State - USSR, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Head Of State - West Germany, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Head Of State - Yugoslavia, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Helicopter, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Illness - President, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Inauguration, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Inauguration, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Inauguration, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Julie - Activities, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Julie - Activities, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Julie and David - Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Key Biscayne, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Labor Leaders, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Last Days, August 7-9, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Last Days, August 7-9, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Law Enforcement, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Marriots, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Mayors, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Mrs. Pat Nixon Activities, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Mrs. Pat Nixon Activities, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Mrs. Pat Nixon Activities, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Mrs. Pat Nixon Activities, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Mrs. Nixon Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - National Security Council, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Past Presidents, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Photo Office - Personal, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Pollution, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - President and Poets, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - President Playing Piano, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - President Walking, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - President's Office - Executive Office Building, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Contact sheets and negatives.
    - Presidential Portraits - Formal, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Presidential Portraits - Informal and Candid, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Presidential Portraits - Informal and Candid, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Presidential Portraits - Informal and Candid, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Presidential Portraits - Informal and Candid, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Presidential Seal, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Presidential Yacht, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Presentations, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Presentations, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Press Conference, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Press Conference, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Press - General, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Press - General, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Press - General, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - San Clemente - Beach, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - San Clemente - Events, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - San Clemente - Events, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - San Clemente - Residence, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - San Clemente - Residence, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Signing Ceremonies, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Signing Ceremonies, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Signing Ceremonies, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Speaking - President, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Speaking - President, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Speaking - President, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Sports, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Sports, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Staff With President - Group, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Staff With President - Group, 1969-1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Staff With President - Group, 1969-1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Staff With President - Individual, 1969-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Staff With President - Individual, 1969-1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Staff With President - Individual, 1969-1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Staff Without President, 1969-1974 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Staff Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Staff Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Staff Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Staff Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Staff Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Staff Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Supreme Court Justices, 1969-1974 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Swearing In Ceremonies, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Swearing In Ceremonies, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Tornado - Xenia, Ohio, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Tricia - Activities, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Tricia - Activities, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Tricia and Ed - Portraits, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Trip To Africa - Mrs. Nixon, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Trip To Azores - Pompidou, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Trip To Bermuda - Heath, 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)